Guide to the Johnson Graduate School of Management Student Activities Office records, 1992-1999.
Johnson Graduate School of Management Student Activities Office records, 1992-1999.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Johnson Graduate School of Management Student Activities Office records, 1992-1999.
26-8-3199.
Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University). Student Activities Office.
2 cubic ft. and 4 videocassettes.
Records, resumes, reports, memoranda, job descriptions and applications, articles, correspondence, notes, calendars, brochures, slides, videocassettes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Student files, correspondence and videos for the Masters in Business Administration (MBA) Program.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Student files, correspondence and videos for the Masters in Business Administration Program, including information on those who participated in the Russian and Japanese exchange and graduate fellowship programs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University).; Cornell University--Graduate Students.; Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University)--Students.
Subjects:
Student activities--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Student exchange programs--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Places:
Japan.; Russia.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videocassettes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Russian Exchange Program
Box 1, folders 1-18
Series II. Japanese Business Program
Box 1, Folders 19-42
Series III. Edmund S. Muskie and Freedom Support Act Graduate Fellowship Program
Box 1, Folders 43-50
Series IV. Central and Eastern Europe Development Program
Box 1, Folders 51-61; Box 2, Folders 1-17
Series V. MBA Enterprise Corps
Box 2, Folders 18-36
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Russian Exchange Program
  - Russian Exchange Program Budget Info., 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Russian Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reform Group, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - SDK Company (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Russian Reforms Personnel Foundation Exchange Program, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Russian Exchange Program, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Russian Exchange Program, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Soviet/Eastern European Initiatives, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Russian Exchange Program, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Russian Exchange Program Budget Information, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Info. Regarding Traveling to Russia, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Russian Program, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Planning/Meeting Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Jim Schmotter's Report, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Protocol of Intent/Calendar of Events, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Students Group Visit, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Russian Academy of Administration, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Series II. Japanese Business Program
  - Student Resume - Bent, Jeffrey, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Student Resume - Bryant, Mark Hager, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Student Resume - Divis, Dean, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Student Resume - Gensheimer, Peter, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Student Resume - Holes, Michael, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Student Resume - Klasell, Timothy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Student Resume - Mould, Timothy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Student Resume - Neuman, Andrew, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Student Resume - Westgarth, John, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Student Resume - Smyth, Francis Scott, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Student Resume - Smith, Ronald, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Student Resume - Spaulding, Suzie, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Evaluation International Management Symposium, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Schedule - Fong, Sy, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Intern Report - Shin Kimura, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Student Resume - Cheng, Grace, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence regarding Tom Sammons, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Japan Resumes, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Japan Resumes, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Japan Program MBAs, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Japan Program MBAs, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Japan Business Programs/Internships, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Japan Business Programs/Internships, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Japan Business Programs/Internships, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Introduction to the Corps, V-551 (Box 3)
  - Introduction to the Corps, 1998-1999; V-552 (Box 3)
  - Russia (original), V-553 (Box 3)
  - Russia (copy), V-554 (Box 3)
  - Durland Lecture - Charles Lee, V-818 (Box 3)
  - Johnson School - Tokyo, 1989; V-1494 (Box 3)
- Series III. Edmund Muskie and Freedom Support Act Graduate Fellowship Program
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Fellow - Lisa Aghamyan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Fellow - Vladimir Ourtchoukine, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Fellow - Igor Siriy, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Fellow - Gytis Kudarauskas, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Fellow - Igor Chlenski, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Information, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Fellow - Dimitri Frolor, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - ACTR/ACCELS Muskie Fellow - D. Faguet, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Series IV. Central and Eastern Europe Development Program
  - CEED Brochures, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - CEED Brochures, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - CEED Applicant Information, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - CEED Applicant Information, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - CEED Applicant Information, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - CEED Information and Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - CEED Information and Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - CEED Summer Applications, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - CEED Summer Applications, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Cornell Business Articles, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - CEED Applicant Information, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - CEED Presentation Slides (Box 2)
  - Entrepreneurship Center Program Information, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Business Plan and Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bulgarian Business News: Correspondence, Notices, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Service Prospective, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Activities, Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CEED Budget Information, Summary of Activities, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Proposal for the Johnson Graduate School of Management, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CEED Participant Reports, Job Descriptions, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Job Descriptions, Handbooks, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Memoranda from Center for European Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - CEED Job Descriptions and Program Reports, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Job Descriptions and Summer Reports By Students, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CEED Memos and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Student Resumes and Acceptance Letters, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Series V. MBA Enterprise Corp.
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Budget and Review of Activities, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Minutes of MBA Executive Meetings, Budget, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Brochure, Review of Activities, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Handbook, Audited Financial Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Job Descriptions and Memos, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Audited Financial Statements, Executive Committee Agenda, MBA Enterprise Corps Brochures, Budget, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Brochure, Correspondence, List of Russian WWW Servers, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Booklet, Review of Activities, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Krakow School of Economics, MBA Enterprise Corps Brochure, MBA Enterprise Corps Profiles, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Travel Itinerary, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Profile and Resume Book, Review of Activities, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Audited Financial Statements, Corps Directory, 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Profile and Resume Book, Review of Activities, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Resumes and Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Student Applications and Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Student Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Student Applications, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - MBA Enterprise Corps Student Applications, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)